[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Parsley is a close relative of the carrot", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first African-American professional baseball player played for Oakland in 1916.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these countries is largest in area?", "correct_answer": "Japan", "incorrect_answers": ["Jordan and Japan are equal in size", "Jordan", "Jamaica"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did the movie The Goonies hit the big screen?", "correct_answer": "1985", "incorrect_answers": ["1982", "1987", "1984"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Denzel Washingtons parents divorced when he was five years old.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All but one of these statements represents a common bond between the movies, The Terminal and Catch Me if You Can.", "correct_answer": "Leonardo DiCaprio stars in them both.", "incorrect_answers": ["They both can be classified as dramas.", "They both are produced by Spielberg.", "Tom Hanks stars in them both."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the First Cat in the Clinton Whitehouse?", "correct_answer": "Socks", "incorrect_answers": ["Alphie", "Monica", "Scallops"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who stars as NYPD police officer John McClane in the hit movie Die Hard?", "correct_answer": "Bruce Willis", "incorrect_answers": ["Tom Cruise", "Harrison Ford", "James Earl Jones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vitamin B6 is widely distributed in foods and its relatively stable form enables it to remain unchanged even when the products are cooked.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If swallowed, ink is harmless.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2003, the FDA issued a warning about a possible connection between green onions and which disease?", "correct_answer": "Hepatitis A", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Gall stones", "Cancer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the nickname of Marilyn Monroes character in the 1959 film Some Like It Hot?", "correct_answer": "Sugar", "incorrect_answers": ["Bubblegum", "Candy", "Muffin"]}]